Finding Aid for Satakunta Region immigrant letters, 1880-1964
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Ikaalinen, letters to
  - Olga Änkö
    - from: Alli Talonen. Detroit, Mich., 1948-1954; 5 items (Reel 5)
  - Elsa Aronen
    - from: Alli Ek. Minn., 1952-1963; 6 items (Reel 5)
  - Tuovi Kujanpää
    - from: Impi Hill., undated; 4 items (Reel 5)
  - Auli Lähteenmäki
    - from: Lyyli Hongisto. Marquette, Mich., 1947-1959; 12 items (Reel 5)
  - Rauha Ojala
    - from: Charles Maki. Fla., 1961; 3 items (Reel 5)
  - Hilja Salomäki
    - from: Ernst Maki. Calif., 1961; 1 items (Reel 5)
  - Taavetti Viitala
    - from: Ivar Viitala., 1960; 1 items (Reel 5)
  - Laura Vilppo
    - from: Emma Tiilinen. Ohio, 1963; 1 items (Reel 5)
  - Taimi Kankaristo
    - from: Lempi Salminen. Mass., 1951-1969; 7 items (Reel 5)
  - Aliina Kivimaki
    - from: Werner Siro. Minn., 1931; 4 items (Reel 5)
  - Elvi Lähteenmäki
    - from: Lempi Salminen. Mass., 1950-1969; 23 items (Reel 5)
  - Erkki Sarkki
    - from: Bruno Sarkki., undated; 1 items (Reel 5)
  - F. Mäkinen
    - from: Aino Vahaniemi. Mass., 1952-1953; 2 items (Reel 5)
    - from: Hilja Vahaniemi. Mass., 1926; 1 items (Reel 5)
  - Erkki Sarkki
    - from: Bruno Sarkki. Wis., 1946; 1 items (Reel 5)
  - Lempi Saunaluoma
    - from: Lydia Gronroos. Conn., 1960-1964; 2 items (Reel 5)
  - Frans Toivola
    - from: Taavetti Toivola. Kenneth, Mich., 1913-1915; 2 items (Reel 5)
  - Reino Haapavuori
    - from: Oskar Vuorinen. N.Y., 1955-1957; 3 items (Reel 5)
  - Hilda Hietamäki
    - from: Lempi Oja. N.Y., Mass., Wash., 1954-1962; 3 items (Reel 5)
  - Elma Lehtimäki
    - from: Amanda Luonssi. N.Y., 1913-1932; 39 items (Reel 5)
    - from: Amanda Luonssi. N.Y., 1932; 58 items (Reel 6)
    - from: Iida Virtanen. N.Y., 1934-1946; 3 items (Reel 6)
    - from: A. Tuuri. Ont., 1946; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Laimi Myllymäki
    - from: Jooseppi Maki. Ont., Alta., undated; 8 items (Reel 6)
    - from: Anni Viita. Ont., 1951-1962; 2 items (Reel 6)
  - Esteri Siuro
    - from: Impi Salonen. Wash., 1947; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Ilmi Viitanen
    - from: Ida Murray. Conn., 1962; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Aino Heiskala
    - from: Hilja Ranta.
      - Marquette, Mich., 1959; 1 items (Reel 6)
      - Ohio, 1960; 5 items (Reel 6)
      - Clawson, Mich., 1961; 1 items (Reel 6)
      - Fla., 1962-1964; 9 items (Reel 6)
  - Tyyne Kuuri
    - from: Tyyne Nummelin. Rock, Mich., 1951; 2 items (Reel 6)
  - Lyyli Mäkelä
    - from: Alvina Maki., undated; 4 items (Reel 6)
    - from: Alexandra Lahti., undated; 6 items (Reel 6)
  - Ilona Sarkki
    - from: Ina Macki. Ill., 1949-1950; 3 items (Reel 6)
  - Arvo Vikman
    - from: Jooseppi Maki. Alta., 1961-1963; 2 items (Reel 6)
    - from: Toini Dromposth. Alta., 1958-1959; 2 items (Reel 6)
  - Elna Peltoniemi
    - from: Vilhelmiina Harju. Minn., 1929; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Aili Ahvenlampi
    - from: Tilda Kilponen. N.Y., 1947; 2 items (Reel 6)
  - Hilda Hietamäki
    - from: H. Hietanen. Conn., 1963; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Suoma Ilomäki
    - fromenpi Kirmo. Munising, Mich., 1963; 3 items (Reel 6)
  - Anna-Liisa Kivinen
    - from: Selja Fleming. Mass., 1946; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Tuovi Kujanpää
    - from: Elli Carlson. Wash., 1964; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Laimi Mäkelä
    - from: Jalmari Kujansuu. Crystal Falls, Mich. (Reel 6)
  - Eino Pitkäkoski
    - from: Robert Koski S.D., 1953; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Lempi Salo
    - from: Ida Maki. Minn., 1947; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Edla Vuorisalo
    - from: Sven Hill. Baraga, Mich., 1946-1953; 6 items (Reel 6)
  - Hillevi Välimäki
    - from: Jenny Koski. N.Y., 1939-1962; 5 items (Reel 6)
  - Martta Välimäki
    - from: Linda Maja. Ont., 1924; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Oskari Alanen
    - from: Hilda Lindell. Que., 1949-1969; 9 items (Reel 6)
  - Amanda Hakala
    - from: Aino Aho. Mass., 1961-1963; 4 items (Reel 6)
  - Hilda Halmela
    - from: Selma Floranta.
      - Ont., Fla., 1947-1964; 22 items (Reel 6)
      - 1961-1962, 2 items (Reel 6)
  - Vieno Hätävara
    - from: Jacob Lake. Oregon., 1946; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Anni Kivimäki
    - from: Sylvia Peippo. Hancock, Mich., 1945; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Sandra Ohramäki
    - from: Selma Eloranta. Ont., Fla., 1960-1963; 11 items (Reel 6)
  - Arvo Riihioja
    - from: Evert Jokiniemi. Pa., undated; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Kustaa Uotila
    - from: Margit Ranta. N.Y., 1963; 3 items (Reel 6)
    - from: Mr. Riuttanen. N.Y., 1961; 1 items (Reel 6)
    - from: Hilja Wilppula. N.Y., 1963; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Tyyne Uotila
    - from: E. Lipponen. N.Y., 1963; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Irene Lempinen
    - from: Martha Wolge. Que., undated; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Markku Isoiitu
    - from: Saima Aho. Ont., 1959-1963; 3 items (Reel 6)
  - Kalle Rantala
    - from: Emilja Peltonen. Ont., 1948; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Arvo, Ala-Nikkilä
    - from: Lauri Ala-Nikkilä. Que., 1925-1933; 3 items (Reel 6)
  - Olga Haavisto
    - from: E. Haavisto. Ont., 1928-1963; 5 items (Reel 6)
  - Reino Niemenmaa
    - from: Konsta Maki. Mass., Ont. (4 items, 1951 (Reel 6)
  - Oiva Haapaniemi
    - from: Eemeli Haavisto. Ont., 1955-1963; 5 items (Reel 6)
  - Eeva Vähäniemi
    - from: Hilja Koskela. Mass., 1947; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Hilma Vilppo
    - from: David Salo. Marquette, Mich., 1963; 3 items (Reel 6)
  - Anna-Liisa Kivinen
    - from: Elli Maki., undated; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Milja Laihonen
    - from: Anni Viita. Ont., 1963-1964; 3 items (Reel 6)
  - Eino Peltonen
    - from: Saima Saari. Ohio, 1925-1927; 3 items (Reel 6)
  - Matti Järvinen
    - from: Aarne Koiste. Quebec, Ont., 1950-1953; 5 items (Reel 6)
  - Anna Alanen
    - from: Unto Lampinen. Ont., 1951-1957; 17 items (Reel 6)
  - Juho Leponiemi
    - from: Ella Viitanen. Ont., 1959; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Toivo Heikkild
    - from: Toini Riutta. Ont., 1959; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Emmi Sjöman
    - from: Kaarina Aaltonen. Ont., N.Y., 1953-1962; 10 items (Reel 6)
  - Maija Rothovius
    - from: Iska Rothovius. Mass., N.Y., 1955-1962; 31 items (Reel 6)
  - Iita Keskinen
    - from: Yrjo Keskinen. Ont., 1951-1962; 4 items (Reel 6)
  - Helka Heikkilä
    - from: Maija Rieslahti. Canada, 1964; 2 items (Reel 6)
  - Aili Lähteenmäki
    - from: Toini Lahteenmaki. Ont., 1957-1958; 2 items (Reel 6)
    - from: Vieno Preston. Ont., 1958-1962; 4 items (Reel 6)
  - Alina Halmela
    - from: Andrew Koski. Minn., 1946; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Evert Jokihaara
    - from: F.E.Lampi. Ill., 1953-1958; 8 items (Reel 6)
- Jämijärvi, letters to
  - Hilja Hautamäki
    - from: Simon Leppanen. Fin, 1913; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Martti Lepistb
    - from: Hilja Maki. Ill., 1940-1964; 4 items (Reel 6)
  - Impi Vuorela
    - from: Frans Kauppila. Mass., 1962; 1 items (Reel 6)
    - from: Jenny Lehto. N.Y., 1963; 1 items (Reel 6)
  - Hanna Vallela
    - from: Vanni Hill. Hancock, Mich., Negaunee, Mich., 1957-1961; 3 items (Reel 6)
  - Frans Koivunen
    - from: Kalle Koivunen. Marquette, Mich., 1923; 1 items (Reel 6)
    - from: Hilja Vainio.Hogstrom, Mich., Rumely, Mich. Mich., 1934-1969; 8 items (Reel 6)
    - from: Hilja Huttula. Mass., 1933; 3 items (Reel 6)
  - Jussi Niemi
    - from: Frans Niemi. N.Y., Pa., 1903-1913; 6 items (Reel 6)
  - Frans Rasi
    - from: Lyydia Launet. Paynesville, Mich. (Reel 7)
  - Martti Rasi
    - from: Lyydia Launet. Paynesville, Mich. (Reel 7)
  - Ida Välimäki
    - from: Sofia Wainio. Ill., 1949-1962; 8 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Mari Heikkila. Mass., 1945-1950; 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Linnea Välimäki
    - from: Hilda Vanka. Ill., 1953; 4 items (Reel 7)
  - Ida Välimäki
    - from: Ida Maki. Ohio, 1956; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Lempi Koski
    - from: Sven Kortemaki. Baraga, Mich., Hancock, Mich. (10 i, 1947-1957 (Reel 7)
  - Hilda Jukola
    - from: Helmi Lahtinen. Republic, Mich., 1929-1936; 14 items (Reel 7)
  - Jussi Kärysoja
    - from: Anselm Oja. Rock, Mich., Princeton, Mich., 1935-1947; 3 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Anselm Helin. Ill., 1962-1963; 4 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Sven Oja. Md., 1935; 2 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Veera Oja. Md., 1935; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Arvo Katajisto
    - from: Pauliina Maraki. D. C., Va., 1946-58, 5 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Hilja Jokinen. Minn. 1944-1963, 5 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Toivo Hedman. Va., 1963; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Kauko Viertola
    - from: Viktor Honkaniemi. N.Y., Fla., 1949-1963; 28 items (Reel 7)
  - Lea Alakoski
    - from: Aino Martin. N.Y., 1962-1963; 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Arvi Kuusijoki
    - from: Tyyra Lindberg. Cal., 1947; 1 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Elimi Eloranta. Fla., 1956; 2 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Irene Eloranta. Fla., 1958; 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Kerttu Mäki
    - from: Hilja Maki. Ill., 1963; 7 items (Reel 7)
  - Jooseppi Palojoki
    - from: Vihtori Kotasalo. N.Y., Ore., 1934-1956; 9 items (Reel 7)
  - Lauri Huosaari
    - from: Kalle Jokinen., undated; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Lyyli Ikola
    - from: Jooseppi Ikola. Ont., 1961; 1 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Konsta Harju. Sault Ste. Marie, Mich., 1927; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Lydia Järvenpää
    - from: Frank Ritakorpi. Negaunee, Mich., Marquette, Mich., 1922-1964; 19 items (Reel 7)
  - Lempi Kivikari
    - from: Mary Katajisto. Ont., Ill., 1948-1963; 4 items (Reel 7)
  - Paavo Niemi
    - from: Frank Maki. Iowa, 1963; 1 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Hilja Vaisanen. Ont., 1962; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Lempi Oja
    - from: Selma Lahti. Minn., 1947; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Nikolai Alakuusijoki
    - from: Jooseppi Maki. Mass., 1958; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Elvi Viitanen
    - from: Sandra Piipponen. Pa., 1954; 2 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Maria Hill. Minn., 1947-1959; 7 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Anna Kallio. Minn., 1949-1958; 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Hilma Viitanen
    - from: Sandra Piipponen. Pa., 1951-1952; 4 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Maria Hill. Mina., 1953; 1 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Anna Kallio. Minn., Alaska, 1947-1962; 4 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Arvo Kallio. Minn., Alaska, Ohio, 1926-1956; 4 items (Reel 7)
  - Hilda Kärysoja
    - from: Hilja Finn. N.Y., 1963; 3 items (Reel 7)
  - Kaarlo Rantasalo, Olavi Katajisto
    - from: Naarle Rantasalo, Emil Tupila.
      - Marquette, Mich., 1962; 1 items (Reel 7)
      - Mass., 1910-1914; 3 items (Reel 7)
  - Pentti Mäkelä
    - from: Hanna Makela. Wash., Ore., Ill., 1920-1963; 9 items (Reel 7)
  - Ringa Raitinpää
    - from: Hilja Nikula. N.Y., Minn., 1961-1963; 8 items (Reel 7)
  - Aune Ketola
    - from: Linda Toyra. Oregon., Miss., 1955-1962; 8 items (Reel 7)
  - Lyyli Harri
    - from: Alina Lammi. Mass., 1915-1949; 12 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Siina Lehtovaara. Rock, Mich., 1946; 1 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Siina Lehtovaara. Rock, Mich., 1946; 1 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Linda Toyra. Ore., 1930-1957; 7 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Sven Jokinen. Ishpeming, Mich., 1914; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Hulda Holma
    - from: John Holma. Munising, Mich., 1911-1919; 4 items (Reel 7)
  - Sauli Holma
    - from: Sandra Holma. Fla., 1958-1959; 4 items (Reel 7)
  - Aino Husaavi
    - from: Santra Kotasalo. Wash., 1935; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Laura Lehtilammi
    - from: Aino Jokelin. Mass., 1956; 3 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Hilja Koskela. Mass., 1960-1963; 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Hilja Mäkinen
    - from: Lempi Kataaki. Dearborn, Mich., 1957; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Selma Palomäki
    - from: Hilda Vienola. Negaunee, Mich., Marquette, Mich., 1945-1958; 6 items (Reel 7)
  - Maija Palonen
    - from: Hanna Savonen. Mass., 1941; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Lauri Rajakorpi
    - from: Kaarlo Lindell. Mass., 1958; 2 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Anni Palmu. Ont., 1949-1961; 5 items (Reel 7)
  - Linnea Rajala
    - from: Hilja Finn. N.Y., 1955; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Rauna Rauha
    - from: Selma Uotila. N.Y., 1950-1958; 5 items (Reel 7)
  - Kaarlo Rantasalo
    - from: Tyyne Ranta. N.Y., 1963; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Helmi Salonen
    - from: Alli Rinnetmaki. Calif., 1963; 3 items (Reel 7)
  - Hanna Viitanen
    - from: Maria Viitanen. Minn., Alaska, 1954-1969; 13 items (Reel 7)
  - Marjatta Viitanen
    - from: Maria Hill. Minn., 1953-1957; 3 items (Reel 7)
  - Hannes Viitaniemi
    - from: Tyyne Lindberg. Md., Cal., 1960-1962; 3 items (Reel 7)
  - Suoma Viitasalo
    - from: Mari Jernstrom. Wash., 1945-1962; 41 items (Reel 7)
  - Toivo Tervalahti, Fanni Alakoski
    - from: Hilja Maki, Emil Koski. Minn., 1964; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Aino Holma
    - from: Alfred Saari. Ont., 1963-1964; 3 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Helmi Brown. Colto:, Wash., 1962-1963; 3 items (Reel 7)
  - Frans Kortesoja
    - from: Lempi Kivela.
      - Marquette, Mich., 1946-1961; 6 items (Reel 7)
      - Ohio, 1948; 1 items (Reel 7)
      - Marquette, Mich. (Reel 7)
  - Toivo Maja
    - from: Alfred Saari. Ont., 1962-1964; 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Ilmi Pursinen
    - from: Edla Karpof. Mass., 1963-1964; 12 items (Reel 7)
  - Kaarlo Rantasalo, Helmi Salone
    - from: Elli Pontinen, Elvira Sten. N.Y., 1963; 4 items (Reel 7)
  - Selma Kivioja
    - from Lydia Stein. Fla., 1962-1964; 3 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Tyyne Kujala. Ont., 1964; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Iivari Pihlaaa
    - from: Hilda Hill. Maine, 1963; 3 items (Reel 7)
  - Kalle Niemi
    - from: Sven Niemi. Gwinn, Mich., 1937-1947; 6 items (Reel 7)
  - Lempi Lahdensuu
    - from: Arvo Heiska. Ont., 1961-1963; 3 items (Reel 7)
  - Ruth Teelmäki
    - from: Alfred Saari. Ont., 1961-1963; 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Impi Laitajdrvi
    - from: Joe Koski. Trenary, Mich., 1946-1951; 2 items (Reel 7)
  - Lempi Lähteenmäki
    - from: Joseph Maki. Skandia, Mich., 1936; 1 items (Reel 7)
  - Vihtori Lähteenmäki
    - from: Oskar Maki. Mass., 1946-1969; 2 items (Reel 7)
    - from: Aina Nurmi. Ont., Ill., Minn., 1914-1946; 7 items (Reel 7)
  - Toini Mansukoski
    - from: H. Levanpaa. Wis., 1950-1964; 6 items (Reel 8)
  - Aune Vglimaa
    - from: Selma Kotila. N.Y., 1961-1964; 32 items (Reel 8)
  - Kaarina Kivioja
    - from: Suoma Nomi. B.C., 1958; 1 items (Reel 8)
  - Jaakko Rantasalo
    - from: Kaarle Rantasalo. photos, 6 items (Reel 8)
  - Tauno Salonen
    - from Lydia Saukkola,. Mass., 1953-1959; 5 items (Reel 8)
  - Elli Mäkelä
    - from: Emilia Lindstrom, Anna Nelson, Anton Lehto Aino Forstrom. N.Y., 1951-1962; 19 items (Reel 8)
  - Ida Halmela
    - from: Ida Ranta. N.Y., 1946-1959; 6 items (Reel 8)
    - from: Ida Ranta. N.Y., 1946-1956; 6 items (Reel 8)
  - Uuno Heiska
    - from: Arvo Heiska
      - Rapid River, Mich., 1955; 1 items (Reel 8)
      - Ont., 1960-1963; 3 items (Reel 8)
  - Vihtori Honkaniemi
    - from: Jakob Laakkonen. Minn., 1957; 1 items (Reel 8)
  - The Town of Jämijärvi
    - from: Suoma Nomi. B.C:, 1957-1963; 3 items (Reel 8)
  - Taimi Järventausta
    - from: Anneli Haukka. Ont., 1963; 1 items (Reel 8)
  - Suoma Laihokari
    - from: Ida Karkkainen. Mass., 1958; 1 items (Reel 8)
  - Pauli Lehtonen
    - from: Frans Kari. Ont., 1912; 1 items (Reel 8)
  - Jussi Niemi
    - from: Aino Niemi. Ohio, 1946-1961; 6 items (Reel 8)
  - Hilda Pitkäkoski
    - from: photo, 1 items (Reel 8)
    - from: Kustaa Uotila. Fla., 1948; 1 items (Reel 8)
    - from: Hilda Koski. N.Y., Sweden, 1955; 3 items (Reel 8)
  - Reijo Rajakallio
    - from: Kalle Heiskala. Fla., 1956; 2 items (Reel 8)
  - Suoma Rajamäki
    - from: Antti Penttila. Soviet Union, 1963; 2 items (Reel 8)
  - Viljo Ruoka
    - from: Suoma Nomi. B.C., 1963; 1 items (Reel 8)
  - Suoma Syrjätie
    - from: Emma Friimaki. Ill., 1962; 1 items (Reel 8)
    - from: Irma Jablonic. Wis., 1963; 1 items (Reel 8)
  - Martta Uusitalo
    - from: Kalle Heiskala. Ont; Fla., Conn., 1952-1957; 16 items (Reel 8)
  - Priska Uusitalo
    - from: Irma Jablonic. Wis., Ill., 1963-1964; 2 items (Reel 8)
  - Ellen Rajakorpi
    - from: Lauri Lindell. Mass., 1961; 1 items (Reel 8)
  - Miina Hakala
    - from: Arvo Hakala. N.J., N.Y., 1948-1952; 2 items (Reel 8)
    - from: Laimi Hakala. Maine, Conn., N.Y., Fla., 1947; 34 items (Reel 8)
    - from: Selma Kotila. N.Y., 1948-1952; 8 items (Reel 8)
    - from: Eemil Hakala, Kalle Heiskala. (Reel 8)
  - Juhani Kulmala
    - from: Anna Wainio. Cal., 1959; 1 items (Reel 8)
  - Anna Mäkynen
    - from: Selma Eloranta. Ont., Fla., 1948-1961; 9 items (Reel 8)
  - Katri Sillanpää
    - from: Lauri Lindell. Scot, 1960; 2 items (Reel 8)
  - Eino Tuuri
    - from: Lyyli Niemi. Ohio, 1958-1963; 3 items (Reel 8)
  - Maija-Liisa Katajisto
    - from: Jooseppi Tupila. Ont., 1953; 1 items (Reel 8)
    - from: Pentti Kujansuu. Ont., 1961; 1 items (Reel 8)
  - Marja-Liisa Mäensivu
    - from: Hilda Ypya. Ont., 1963-1964; 4 items (Reel 8)
  - Lempi Mäkitalo
    - from: Hilda Jokinen. Ore., 1935-1956; 5 items (Reel 8)
  - Annikki Viitanen
    - from: Maria Hill. Minn., 1958-1963; 6 items (Reel 8)
  - Lahja Kulmala
    - from: Anna Vainio. Cal., 1954; 1 items (Reel 8)
  - Arja Rajala
    - from: Kari Myllymaki. Ont., 1962-1963; 4 items (Reel 8)
  - Hilja Rinnemäki
    - from: Alviina Halkere. N.Y., 1961; 4 items (Reel 8)
  - Arvi Holma
    - from: Ensio Hanel. Col., 1959-1962; 3 items (Reel 8)
  - Lempi Lepistö
    - from: Reino Kinnunen
      - Watton, Mich. (l items), 1946 (Reel 8)
      - Maine, undated; 1 items (Reel 8)
      - Manistee, Mich., 1961-1963; 2 items (Reel 8)
  - Lempi Tasala
    - from: Mary Smith., undated; 3 items (Reel 8)
- Kankaanpää, letters to
  - Arvi Stengård
    - from: Sidney Rowe. Ironwood, Mich., 1960; 1 items (Reel 8)
  - Frans Gasniemi
    - from: Maria Nisumaa. N.Y., 1958-1969; 5 items (Reel 8)
  - Anni Rajala
    - from: Josefiina Maki. Ohio, 1951; 1 items (Reel 8)
  - Aino Ranne
    - from: Marv Jernstrom. Wash., 1960; 4 items (Reel 8)
  - Alli Kivioja
    - from: V. K. Kaivo. Wash, 1958; 1 items (Reel 8)
    - from: Alli Kaivo. Wash., 1947; 1 items (Reel 8)
  - Hilja Fami
    - from: Iida Koski. Mass., 1947-1964; 51 items (Reel 8)
  - Arvo Riihiluoma
    - from: Hilda Kolu. Detroit, Mich., 1912-1962; 3 items (Reel 8)
  - Kalle Andelin
    - from: Oskari Andelin. Minn., 1951; 1 items (Reel 8)
    - from: Frans Andelin
      - Wakefield, Mich. (l items), 1928 (Reel 8)
      - Wis., 1953-1955; 10 items (Reel 8)
    - from: Matti Andelin. Palmer, Mich., 1947-1961; 7 items (Reel 8)
    - from: Matti Andelin. Minn., Mass., N.Y., 1908-1931; 6 items (Reel 9)
  - Lempi Välimäki
    - from: J. Maki. Ont., 1949; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Paavo Huhtamäki
    - from: Anna Ahlrot. Ohio, 1960-1962; 2 items (Reel 9)
  - Liisa Panttila
    - from: Eero Tuomanen. Mass., 1949; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Vilhelmiina Haapala
    - from: John Lamminen. Mass., Vt., 1955-1962; 7 items (Reel 9)
  - Mika Anonen
    - from: Richard Nordlund. photo, 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Sakari Tommila
    - from: Oskari Tommila. N.H., 1947; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Svante Tommila
    - from: Aune Matson. N.H. (l items), 1954 (Reel 9)
  - Lily Pihlajaniemi
    - from: Hilda Lindell. N.Y., Mass., 1920-1961; 2 items (Reel 9)
  - Silja Rajala
    - from: Olga Hupponen. Ont., 1963; 2 items (Reel 9)
  - Esteri Juhantalo
    - from: Hilja Taavela
      - Mass., 1959-1962; 3 items (Reel 9)
      - Rock, Mich., Detroit, Mich., 1963; 2 items (Reel 9)
      - Wash., Mass., 1964; 7 items (Reel 9)
      - Detroit, Mich., 1964; 3 items (Reel 9)
  - Kirsti Löytäkorpi
    - from: Anni Doyen. N.Y., 1959-1964; 5 items (Reel 9)
  - Martta Rinne
    - from: Vaino Heikkila. Ont., 1948-1949; 3 items (Reel 9)
  - unknown
    - from: Kauko Husari. Oregon., 1959; 2 items (Reel 9)
  - Kaarina Stengård
    - from: Aune Lillemal., 1958-1959; 2 items (Reel 9)
  - Hanna Jylli
    - from: Veikko Jylli. B.C., 1962; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Kirsti Luoma
    - from: Pirkko Votaja. Ont., 1961; 1 items (Reel 9)
- Karkku, letters to
  - Kalle Kutsi
    - from: Aksel Kutsi. Raittiuskansan Kalenteri [Calendar for. Temperance Society], 1898; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Eva Mäkinen
    - from: Eemeli Nurmi. Minn., 1946-1955; 6 items (Reel 9)
  - Kalle Ruusunen
    - from: Jalmari Maki. Mont., 1941-1963; 12 items (Reel 9)
  - Lyyli Lehtimäki
    - from: Juha Lehtimäki., undated; 2 items (Reel 9)
  - Martta Helin, Eino Lehtinen. Rauha Prusi
    - from: Julia Blomberg, Vaino Lehtinen, Elsa Lehtinen, Aino Grandell. Mass., 1942-1959; 5 items (Reel 9)
  - Tauno Simula
    - from: Aino Grandell. Mass., 1951-1953; 2 items (Reel 9)
  - Ville Suojanen, Kalle Hurula
    - from: Vilhelm Suojanen, Kalle Leikkanen. Mass., 1932-1933; 2 items (Reel 9)
  - Kalle Hurula, Maija Koski
    - from: Lempi Leikkanen, Hilma Salenski. Ont., 1941-1962; 2 items (Reel 9)
  - Yrjö Koskinen, Emma Järvenpää
    - from: Hilja Laitinen, Mimmi Salmeen, Saku Marjamaki. Mass., 1956-1962; 8 items (Reel 9)
  - Kalle Järvenpää
    - from: Paavo Marjamaki., undated; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Arvo Leikkaa
    - from: Heikki Leikas. N. Y., 1933; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Kaarina Savart
    - from: Sylvia Klaiber. Que., 1951-1962; 5 items (Reel 9)
  - Suoma Vesanto
    - from: Lauri Nurminen. Ont., 1928; 30 items (Reel 9)
  - Martta Aalto
    - from: Antero Aalto. Calif., Wash., 1905-1963; 26 items (Reel 9)
- Karvia, letters to
  - Hermanni Mustajärvi
    - from: Matti Salmi. Oregon., 1929; 1 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Lempi Koski. Ont., 1951; 1 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Salomon Jakobson. Minn., 1926; 1 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Emilia Torma. Watton, Mich., 1946; 1 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Hilma Ylinen. Mont., 1934; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Vilhelm Rantaniemi
    - from: Joseph Jokinen. Hancock, Mich., 1938; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Svante Peltoniemi
    - from: Nikolai Nieminen, 1890; 1 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Nikolai Lautamaki. Mont., 1895; 3 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Johannes Peltoniemi. Wash., 1923; 1 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Nikolai Peltoniemi. Wash., Cal., 1916-1919; 3 items (Reel 9)
  - Hilda Ojanperä
    - from: Viljam Maki. Minn., 1893; 1 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Erkki Hautala. Mont., 1901-1910; 3 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Vihtori Hautala. Wash., 1910-1947; 3 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Ville Hautala. Mont., Ore., 1899-1951; 7 items (Reel 9)
  - Rauha Nikkola
    - from: Julia Huhta Mäki., undated; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Elma Perä
    - from: Joe Hendrikson. Oregon., 1920-1924; 4 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Johannes Aalto. Calumet, Mich., 1920; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Gunilla Lehtinen
    - from: from: K. Hartman. England, Minn., Ont., 1929-1951; 7 items (Reel 9)
  - Juho Vähätalo
    - from: from: K. Hartman. Minn., 1948-1959; 3 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Mimmi Vähatalo. Ont. 1951-1962, 4 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Eini Tulonen. Ont., 1947-1964; 7 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Anni Pocaluyko. Ont., 1959-1964; 6 items (Reel 9)
  - Hilma Marjasuo
    - from: Emil Ruska. Fla., 1958-1964; 6 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Hulda Otava. Minn., undated; 3 items (Reel 9)
  - Ilkka Nims
    - from: Vaino Makynen. Ont., 1948; 4 items (Reel 9)
  - Satu Rantala
    - from: Svante Codell. Chassell, Mich., 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Aili Hälli
    - from: Aili Lustig. Wash., 1945-1963; 7 items (Reel 9)
  - Hilja Penttilä
    - from: Jonathan Seppala. Ont., Soviet Union, 1905-1959; 3 items (Reel 9)
  - Reino Haanpää
    - from: Hulda Mustola. Oregon., 1945-1950; 2 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Viljo Haanpaa. Ont., 1955; 1 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Elma Kallio. Ont., 1959; 2 items (Reel 9)
  - Maria Halme
    - from: Amalia Papunen., undated; 2 items (Reel 9)
  - Serafia Keskinen
    - from: Matilda Maenpaa. Minn., Ont., 1958; 2 items (Reel 9)
  - Martta Koivula
    - from: Sylvia Bokovoy. Minn., 1959; 3 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Selma Mendelin. Ont., 1964; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Emma Mukka
    - from: Maria Gadell. Watton, Mich., 1945; 14 items (Reel 9)
  - Tilda Salo
    - from: Lulda Elovaara. Mass., 1946-1955; 4 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Maurits Elova. Mass., 1945-1955; 6 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Sylvia Sjoman. Mass., 1947; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Lauara Alavia
    - from: Selma Lampi. Wash., 1958; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Oskari Hulkko
    - from: Anselmi Hulkko., 1912; 2 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Otto Malinen. Ont., 1911; 6 items (Reel 9)
    - from: A. Mauerer. Detroit, Mich., 1908; 2 items (Reel 9)